Contact

8460921201 (Mobile) ravipansuriya786@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ravipansuriya (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Communication

Mockups

Typography

Languages

English (Limited Working)

Gujarati (Native or Bilingual)

Hindi (Full Professional)

Certifications

Introduction to Programming Using JavaScript

CompTIA Network+

CompTIA IT Fundamentals+

Ravi Pansuriya

UI UX / Frontend Developer at Logix Built Infotech

Surat, Gujarat, India

Summary

I am a Front End developer with industry experience building websites and web applications. I have professional experience working with HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, and Angular. I also have experience working with WordPress, tailwindcss, and React JS.

Experience

Logix Built Infotech
UI UX / Frontend Developer
December 2020 - Present (3 years 7 months)

Surat, Gujarat, India

- > Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure.
- > Working with different content management systems.
- > Solve HTML and CSS bugs on the website.
- > Testing and improving the design of the website.
- > Design Logos, Banners, Flyers, etc
- > Provide daily reports to respective persons.

ivn24news

Video and Graphic Designer January 2019 - December 2020 (2 years) Surat, Gujarat, India

- > Create infographics and presentation materials to simplify the communication of complex concepts and data.
- > Provide technical support for design- and video-related efforts.
- > Edit video clips for use on social media platforms.
- > Maintain organized content files, and help to organize and archive existing video and graphics files.

Shreeji Multimedia Education Graphic Designer July 2018 - January 2019 (7 months) Katargam

> Develop illustrations, logos and other designs using software.

- > Use the appropriate colors and layouts for each graphic
- > Study design briefs and determine requirements

Education

Board Infinity

Full Stack Web Development, Full Stack · (February 2022 - August 2022)

Ambaba Commerce College, Maniba Institute of Business Management & Deviba Institute of Computer Application B.Com · (January 2019 - May 2019)